{
    "subject": "resource/Mark_Rydell",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1928",
    "human_readable": "Mark Rydell was born in 1928.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.88204425573349,
            "question": "In what year was Mark Rydell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118515610694885,
            "question": "Where was Mark Rydell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6722066402435303,
            "question": "Is there a biography written about Mark Rydell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5807718634605408,
            "question": "What is Mark Rydell's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5382715463638306,
            "question": "What is Mark Rydell known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4415901005268097,
            "question": "Is Mark Rydell still alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3814675807952881,
            "question": "Was Mark Rydell a famous director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22251705825328827,
            "question": "Has Mark Rydell acted in any movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2027096003293991,
            "question": "Did Mark Rydell win any awards for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13834798336029053,
            "question": "What movies has Mark Rydell directed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mark Rydell was born in 1928.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6001_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Mark Rydell win any awards for his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6001_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Mark Rydell acted in any movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6001_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Mark Rydell a famous director?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6001_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6001_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The query asks whether Mark Rydell was born in 1928, according to the provided context information.\n* Upon reviewing the documents, we find that his birthdate is mentioned multiple times as March 23, 1929 (not 1928) in the following files:\n\t+ file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6001/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt\n\t+ file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6001/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt\n\t+ file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6001/re-ranker-msmarco/84.txt\n* Therefore, the information in the documents does not support the query that Mark Rydell was born in 1928."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide conflicting information regarding the birth year of Mark Rydell. Some sources state he was born on March 23, 1928, while others indicate his birth year as 1929. Therefore, the statement that he was born in 1928 is not supported by all the documents provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The birth year of Mark Rydell, as provided in the context information, is 1929.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}